Welcome to the night, the card's laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Whoa
Hearts and the balance
Every card an open door
Feel the romance
In every arcane world
Hey guys
It's getting a little bit kind of like half a week half asleep feeling
Which one's we but I think I'm pretty much out of we know hi guys, how's everybody? Yeah, we guys are coming in
Hope I'm not been too weird today. I did have to delete the last string because
including 30 times nipples, but let's put that on the eyes now.
Hi guys, you hear me okay? Tommy, can you hear me?
Hello, do you hear me? Yes, you hear me. Hi guys, how's everybody doing?
Am I looking too weird today?
Hey, what's up, thing that is there's my serious bunkies,
mechanics, sorry, guys, members.
Thank you guys.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, I don't think I trust this guy.
I don't know that name, it's not the name of a nice person, it's a form of my name.
What the hell?
I don't know, are you too tired to just sit on this one?
Okay, let's do it over there.
Okay.
What happened on the gas?
Okay, I'm gonna slap it.
I'm so sorry, I need an IDP.
Oh, here we go.
Once again, make sure this person's on the up and up, up, up, up, up.
Nope, he wasn't.
Oh, he was a porn bomber, too.
Hi, you're too fast and I'm really stupid for more.
Oh, don't worry, you're not gonna get one.
嗯... 嗯... 嗯... 嗯... 嗯... 嗯...
Oh my gosh.
Let's wait.
You guys can talk for a while.
I'm sorry.
I'll let you guys talk for a while.
Hmm